<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CakeDescriptionApp</string>

    <string name="coffee_cake">Coffee Cake</string>
    <string name="banana_cake">Banana Cake</string>
    <string name="funfettti_cake">Funfetti cake</string>
    <string name="pineapple">Pineapple Upside Down cake</string>
    <string name="lemon_cake">Lemon Cake</string>
    <string name="black_forest_cake">Black Forest Cake</string>
    <string name="cheese_cake">Cheesecake</string>

    <string name="coffee_cake_des">This cake comes as a perfect dessert for coffee lovers.
        They are delicious and are available in multiple coffee flavours such as Irish and Mocha.</string>
    <string name="banana_cake_des">The cake flavour that makes you go bananas is the banana cake at the ninth spot.
        It has a moist texture and an incredibly strong taste.</string>
    <string name="funfettti_cake_des">Funfetti is a fun-filled and joyous cake that has garnered lots of love from people and hence has also found the eighth spot in this list. Brimming with colourful sprinklers,
        inside and out, Funfetti is a great birthday cake. Agreed?</string>
    <string name="pineapple_des">Pineapple is an excellent ingredient for desserts, and hence, the upside-down pineapple cake being a part of this list at number seven doesn’t come as a surprise.
        The cake throws a refreshing taste into your mouth, and it looks just as beautiful.</string>
    <string name="lemon_cake_des">A simple but all-time favourite, lemon cake enjoys the sixth number spot in this top ten list. While we love icing lemon cakes with many fun ideas for birthdays and other celebrations,
        we also love having a few pieces of it at home with coffee.</string>
    <string name="black_forest_cake_des">At number five,black forest cake is a variety which is full of all the best ingredients. This cake has chocolate, it is sweet, and it has cherries on the top.
        Black forest cake looks appealing to the eyes and tastes pleasing to the tongue.</string>
    <string name="cheese_cake_des">Cheesecake ranks at number four as it is loved for being so creamy and yummy. When made well, mixed with the right flavours,
        cheesecake can easily delight even the most delicate taste bud of your mouth.</string>


</resources>